{"Questions": { "Question #201 Topic 1":{ "question":"According to the AWS shared responsibility model, what is AWS responsible for?", "answers":[ "A. Configuring Amazon VPC", "B. Managing application code", "C. Maintaining application traffic", "CORRECT:D. Managing the network infrastructure"],"explanation": "Reference: https://cloudacademy.com/blog/aws-shared-responsibility-model-security/","discussions": "4"}, "Question #202 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which service should be used to estimate the costs of running a new project on AWS?", "answers":[ "A. AWS TCO Calculator", "B. AWS Simple Monthly Calculator", "CORRECT:C. AWS Cost Explorer API", "D. AWS Budgets"],"explanation": "To forecast your costs, use the AWS Cost Explorer. Use cost allocation tags to divide your resources into groups, and then estimate the costs for each group. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/estimating-aws-resource-costs/","discussions": "19"}, "Question #203 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS tool will identify security groups that grant unrestricted Internet access to a limited list of ports?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Organizations", "B. AWS Trusted Advisor", "C. AWS Usage Report", "CORRECT:D. Amazon EC2 dashboard"],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.cloudconformity.com/knowledge-base/aws/EC2/security-group-egress-any.html","discussions": "21"}, "Question #204 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service can be used to generate alerts based on an estimated monthly bill?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Config", "CORRECT:B. Amazon CloudWatch", "C. AWS X-Ray", "D. AWS CloudTrail"],"explanation": "You can monitor your estimated AWS charges by using Amazon CloudWatch. When you enable the monitoring of estimated charges for your AWS account, the estimated charges are calculated and sent several times daily to CloudWatch as metric data. Billing metric data is stored in the US East (N. Virginia) Region and represents worldwide charges. This data includes the estimated charges for every service in AWS that you use, in addition to the estimated overall total of your AWS charges. Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/monitor_estimated_charges_with_cloudwatch.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #205 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which Amazon EC2 pricing model offers the MOST significant discount when compared to On-Demand Instances?", "answers":[ "A. Partial Upfront Reserved Instances for a 1-year term", "B. All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 1-year term", "CORRECT:C. All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term", "D. No Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #206 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is the responsibility of AWS?", "answers":[ "A. Setting up AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) users and groups", "CORRECT:B. Physically destroying storage media at end of life", "C. Patching guest operating systems", "D. Configuring security settings on Amazon EC2 instances"],"explanation": "Media storage devices used to store customer data are classified by AWS as Critical and treated accordingly, as high impact, throughout their life-cycles. AWS has exacting standards on how to install, service, and eventually destroy the devices when they are no longer useful. When a storage device has reached the end of its useful life, AWS decommissions media using techniques detailed in NIST 800-88. Media that stored customer data is not removed from AWS control until it has been securely decommissioned. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-center/controls/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #207 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is an advantage of using AWS?", "answers":[ "A. AWS audits user data.", "B. Data is automatically secure.", "C. There is no guessing on capacity needs.", "CORRECT:D. AWS manages compliance needs."],"explanation": "AWS manages dozens of compliance programs in its infrastructure. This means that segments of your compliance have already been completed. Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/latest/aws-overview/security-and-compliance.html","discussions": "19"}, "Question #208 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service would a customer use with a static website to achieve lower latency and high transfer speeds?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Lambda", "B. Amazon DynamoDB Accelerator", "C. Amazon Route 53", "CORRECT:D. Amazon CloudFront"],"explanation": "Amazon CloudFront is a fast content delivery network (CDN) service that securely delivers data, videos, applications, and APIs to customers globally with low latency, high transfer speeds, all within a developer-friendly environment. CloudFront is integrated with AWS '' both physical locations that are directly connected to the AWS global infrastructure, as well as other AWS services. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #209 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which services manage and automate application deployments on AWS? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. AWS Elastic Beanstalk", "CORRECT:B. AWS CodeCommit", "CORRECT:C. AWS Data Pipeline", "D. AWS CloudFormation", "E. AWS Config"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/tutorials/continuous-deployment-pipeline/","discussions": "27"}, "Question #210 Topic 1":{ "question":"A user wants guidance on possible savings when migrating from on-premises to AWS. Which tool is suitable for this scenario?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Budgets", "B. Cost Explorer", "CORRECT:C. AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator", "D. AWS Well-Architected Tool"],"explanation": "The TCO Calculator provides directional guidance on possible realized savings when deploying AWS. This tool is built on an underlying calculation model, that generates a fair assessment of value that a customer may achieve given the data provided by the user. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #211 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which principles are used to architect applications for reliability on the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Design for automated failure recovery", "B. Use multiple Availability Zones", "CORRECT:C. Manage changes via documented processes", "D. Test for moderate demand to ensure reliability", "E. Backup recovery to an on-premises environment"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/apn/the-5-pillars-of-the-aws-well-architected-framework/","discussions": "38"}, "Question #212 Topic 1":{ "question":"What tasks should a customer perform when that customer suspects an AWS account has been compromised? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Rotate passwords and access keys.", "B. Remove MFA tokens.", "C. Move resources to a different AWS Region.", "D. Delete AWS CloudTrail Resources.", "CORRECT:E. Contact AWS Support."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/potential-account-compromise/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #213 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is an example of high availability in the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. Consulting AWS technical support at any time day or night", "CORRECT:B. Ensuring an application remains accessible, even if a resource fails", "C. Making any AWS service available for use by paying on demand", "D. Deploying in any part of the world using AWS Regions"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/startups/high-availability-for-mere-mortals/","discussions": "12"}, "Question #214 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS security service protects applications from distributed denial of service attacks with always-on detection and automatic inline mitigations?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Inspector", "B. AWS Web Application Firewall (AWS WAF)", "C. Elastic Load Balancing (ELB)", "CORRECT:D. AWS Shield"],"explanation": "AWS Shield is a managed Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection service that safeguards applications running on AWS. AWS Shield provides always-on detection and automatic inline mitigations that minimize application downtime and latency, so there is no need to engage AWS Support to benefit from DDoS protection. There are two tiers of AWS Shield - Standard and Advanced. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/shield/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #215 Topic 1":{ "question":"A company wants to monitor the CPU usage of its Amazon EC2 resources. Which AWS service should the company use?", "answers":[ "A. AWS CloudTrail", "CORRECT:B. Amazon CloudWatch", "C. AWS Cost and Usage report", "D. Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)"],"explanation": "With Basic monitoring you get data on your cloudwatch metrics every 5 minutes. Enabling detailed monitoring, you will get the data every one minute. To check if detailed monitoring is enabled, on your EC2 Console, Select the instance, on the lower plane, Select Monitoring. Reference: https://forums.aws.amazon.com/thread.jspa?threadID=263876","discussions": "9"}, "Question #216 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is an AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) role?", "answers":[ "A. A user associated with an AWS resource", "B. A group associated with an AWS resource", "CORRECT:C. An entity that defines a set of permissions for use with an AWS resource", "D. An authentication credential associated with a multi-factor authentication (MFA) token"],"explanation": "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) enables you to manage access to AWS services and resources securely. Using IAM, you can create and manage AWS users and groups, and use permissions to allow and deny their access to AWS resources. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/iam/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #217 Topic 1":{ "question":"What are the advantages of Reserved Instances? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. They provide a discount over on-demand pricing.", "B. They provide access to additional instance types.", "C. They provide additional networking capability.", "D. Customers can upgrade instances as new types become available.", "CORRECT:E. Customers can reserve capacity in an Availability Zone."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/ec2-ri-basics/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #218 Topic 1":{ "question":"How do Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling groups help achieve high availability for a web application?", "answers":[ "A. They automatically add more instances across multiple AWS Regions based on global demand of the application.", "CORRECT:B. They automatically add or replace instances across multiple Availability Zones when the application needs it.", "C. They enable the application's static content to reside closer to end users.", "D. They are able to distribute incoming requests across a tier of web server instances."],"explanation": "When the unhealthy Availability Zone returns to a healthy state, Auto Scaling automatically redistributes the application instances evenly across all of the designated Availability Zones. Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/ec2/userguide/auto-scaling-benefits.html","discussions": "9"}, "Question #219 Topic 1":{ "question":"How can one AWS account use Reserved Instances from another AWS account?", "answers":[ "A. By using Amazon EC2 Dedicated Instances", "CORRECT:B. By using AWS Organizations consolidated billing", "C. By using the AWS Cost Explorer tool", "D. By using AWS Budgets"],"explanation": "The account that originally purchased the Reserved Instance receives the discount first. If the purchasing account doesn't have any instances that match the terms of the Reserved Instance, the discount for the Reserved Instance is assigned to any matching usage on another account in the organization. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/ec2-ri-consolidated-billing/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #220 Topic 1":{ "question":"A customer runs an On-Demand Amazon Linux EC2 instance for 3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds. For how much time will the customer be billed?", "answers":[ "A. 3 hours, 5 minutes", "B. 3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds", "C. 3 hours, 6 minutes", "CORRECT:D. 4 hours"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/ec2-instance-hour-billing/","discussions": "37"}, "Question #221 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following AWS services provide compute resources? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Lambda", "CORRECT:B. Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)", "C. AWS CodeDeploy", "D. Amazon Glacier", "E. AWS Organizations"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/latest/aws-overview/compute-services.html","discussions": "10"}, "Question #222 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service enables users to deploy infrastructure as code by automating the process of provisioning resources?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon GameLift", "CORRECT:B. AWS CloudFormation", "C. AWS Data Pipeline", "D. AWS Glue"],"explanation": "AWS CloudFormation provides a common language for you to model and provision AWS and third party application resources in your cloud environment. AWS CloudFormation allows you to use programming languages or a simple text file to model and provision, in an automated and secure manner, all the resources needed for your applications across all regions and accounts. This gives you a single source of truth for your AWS and third party resources. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudformation/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #223 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS services provide a way to extend an on-premises architecture to the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Amazon EBS", "CORRECT:B. AWS Direct Connect", "C. Amazon CloudFront", "CORRECT:D. AWS Storage Gateway", "E. Amazon Connect"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #224 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following allows users to provision a dedicated network connection from their internal network to AWS?", "answers":[ "A. AWS CloudHSM", "CORRECT:B. AWS Direct Connect", "C. AWS VPN", "D. Amazon Connect"],"explanation": "AWS Direct Connect lets you establish a dedicated network connection between your network and one of the AWS Direct Connect locations. Using industry standard 802.1q VLANs, this dedicated connection can be partitioned into multiple virtual interfaces. This allows you to use the same connection to access public resources such as objects stored in Amazon S3 using public IP address space, and private resources such as Amazon EC2 instances running within an Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) using private IP space, while maintaining network separation between the public and private environments. Virtual interfaces can be reconfigured at any time to meet your changing needs. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/directconnect/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #225 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which services use AWS edge locations? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon CloudFront", "B. AWS Shield", "CORRECT:C. Amazon EC2", "D. Amazon RDS", "E. Amazon ElastiCache"],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.edureka.co/community/600/what-is-an-edge-location-in-aws","discussions": "25"}, "Question #226 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which service would provide network connectivity in a hybrid architecture that includes the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon VPC", "B. AWS Direct Connect", "C. AWS Directory Service", "D. Amazon API Gateway"],"explanation": "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) is a logically isolated, private section of the AWS Cloud to launch resources in a virtual data center in the cloud. Amazon VPC allows you to leverage multiple Availability Zones (AZ) within a region so that you can build greater fault tolerance within your workloads. You have complete control. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/publicsector/aws-networking-capabilities-gives-you-choices-for-hybrid-cloud-connectivity-but-which-service-works-best- for-your-use-case/","discussions": "28"}, "Question #227 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which tool can be used to compare the costs of running a web application in a traditional hosting environment to running it on AWS?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Cost Explorer", "B. AWS Budgets", "C. AWS Cost and Usage report", "CORRECT:D. AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #228 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is the value of using third-party software from AWS Marketplace instead of installing third-party software on Amazon EC2? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Users pay for software by the hour or month depending on licensing.", "CORRECT:B. AWS Marketplace enables the user to launch applications with 1-Click.", "C. AWS Marketplace data encryption is managed by a third-party vendor.", "D. AWS Marketplace eliminates the need to upgrade to newer software versions.", "E. Users can deploy third-party software without testing."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/partners/aws-marketplace/","discussions": "13"}, "Question #229 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following is a cloud architectural design principle?", "answers":[ "A. Scale up, not out.", "CORRECT:B. Loosely couple components.", "C. Build monolithic systems.", "D. Use commercial database software."],"explanation": "Loosely coupled architectures reduce interdependencies, so that a change or failure in a component does not cascade to other components. Reference: https://aws-certified-cloud-practitioner.fandom.com/wiki/1.3_List_the_different_cloud_architecture_design_principles","discussions": "1"}, "Question #230 Topic 1":{ "question":"Under the shared responsibility model; which of the following areas are the customer's responsibility? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Firmware upgrades of network infrastructure", "CORRECT:B. Patching of operating systems", "C. Patching of the underlying hypervisor", "D. Physical security of data centers", "CORRECT:E. Configuration of the security group"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #231 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which service enables customers to audit and monitor changes in AWS resources?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Trusted Advisor", "B. Amazon GuardDuty", "C. Amazon Inspector", "CORRECT:D. AWS Config"],"explanation": "AWS Config is a service that enables you to assess, audit, and evaluate the configurations of your AWS resources. Config continuously monitors and records your AWS resource configurations and allows you to automate the evaluation of recorded configurations against desired configurations. With Config, you can review changes in configurations and relationships between AWS resources, dive into detailed resource configuration histories, and determine your overall compliance against the configurations specified in your internal guidelines. This enables you to simplify compliance auditing, security analysis, change management, and operational troubleshooting. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/config/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #232 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service identifies security groups that allow unrestricted access to a user's AWS resources?", "answers":[ "A. AWS CloudTrail", "CORRECT:B. AWS Trusted Advisor", "C. Amazon CloudWatch", "D. Amazon Inspector"],"explanation": "","discussions": "6"}, "Question #233 Topic 1":{ "question":"According to the AWS shared responsibility model, who is responsible for configuration management?", "answers":[ "A. It is solely the responsibility of the customer.", "B. It is solely the responsibility of AWS.", "CORRECT:C. It is shared between AWS and the customer.", "D. It is not part of the AWS shared responsibility model."],"explanation": "AWS maintains the configuration of its infrastructure devices, but a customer is responsible for configuring their own guest operating systems, databases, and applications. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #234 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service is a content delivery network that securely delivers data, video, and applications to users globally with low latency and high speeds?", "answers":[ "A. AWS CloudFormation", "B. AWS Direct Connect", "CORRECT:C. Amazon CloudFront", "D. Amazon Pinpoint"],"explanation": "Amazon CloudFront is a fast content delivery network (CDN) service that securely delivers data, videos, applications, and APIs to customers globally with low latency, high transfer speeds, all within a developer-friendly environment. CloudFront is integrated with AWS '' both physical locations that are directly connected to the AWS global infrastructure, as well as other AWS services. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #235 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which benefit of the AWS Cloud supports matching the supply of resources with changing workload demands?", "answers":[ "A. Security", "B. Reliability", "CORRECT:C. Elasticity", "D. High availability"],"explanation": "Reference: https://wa.aws.amazon.com/wat.map.en.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #236 Topic 1":{ "question":"A user is running an application on AWS and notices that one or more AWS-owned IP addresses is involved in a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack. Who should the user contact FIRST about this situation?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Premium Support", "B. AWS Technical Account Manager", "C. AWS Solutions Architect", "CORRECT:D. AWS Abuse team"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/report-aws-abuse/","discussions": "6"}, "Question #237 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which of the following are benefits of hosting infrastructure in the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. There are no upfront commitments.", "CORRECT:B. AWS manages all security in the cloud.", "CORRECT:C. Users have the ability to provision resources on demand.", "D. Users have access to free and unlimited storage.", "E. Users have control over the physical infrastructure."],"explanation": "","discussions": "31"}, "Question #238 Topic 1":{ "question":"What AWS service would be used to centrally manage AWS access policies across multiple accounts?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Service Catalog", "B. AWS Config", "C. AWS Trusted Advisor", "CORRECT:D. AWS Organizations"],"explanation": "AWS Organizations helps you centrally govern your environment as you grow and scale your workloads on AWS. Whether you are a growing startup or a large enterprise, Organizations helps you to centrally manage billing; control access, compliance, and security; and share resources across your AWS accounts. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/organizations/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #239 Topic 1":{ "question":"What is AWS Trusted Advisor?", "answers":[ "A. It is an AWS staff member who provides recommendations and best practices on how to use AWS.", "B. It is a network of AWS partners who provide recommendations and best practices on how to use AWS.", "CORRECT:C. It is an online tool with a set of automated checks that provides recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security.", "D. It is another name for AWS Technical Account Managers who provide recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security."],"explanation": "AWS Trusted Advisor is an online tool that provides you real time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices. Whether establishing new workflows, developing applications, or as part of ongoing improvement, take advantage of the recommendations provided by Trusted Advisor on a regular basis to help keep your solutions provisioned optimally. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #240 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service or feature allows a company to visualize, understand, and manage AWS costs and usage over time?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Budgets", "CORRECT:B. AWS Cost Explorer", "C. AWS Organizations", "D. Consolidated billing"],"explanation": "AWS Cost Explorer has an easy-to-use interface that lets you visualize, understand, and manage your AWS costs and usage over time. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/aws-cost-management/aws-cost-explorer/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #241 Topic 1":{ "question":"Which AWS service offers on-demand access to AWS security and compliance reports?", "answers":[ "A. AWS CloudTrail", "CORRECT:B. AWS Artifact", "C. AWS Health", "D. Amazon CloudWatch"],"explanation": "AWS Artifact is your go-to, central resource for compliance-related information that matters to you. It provides on-demand access to AWS' security and compliance reports and select online agreements. Reports available in AWS Artifact include our Service Organization Control (SOC) reports, Payment Card Industry (PCI) reports, and certifications from accreditation bodies across geographies and compliance verticals that validate the implementation and operating effectiveness of AWS security controls. Agreements available in AWS Artifact include the Business Associate Addendum (BAA) and the Nondisclosure Agreement (NDA). Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/artifact/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #1 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS services can host a Microsoft SQL Server database? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon EC2", "CORRECT:B. Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS)", "C. Amazon Aurora", "D. Amazon Redshift", "E. Amazon S3"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/sql/","discussions": "15"}, "Question #2 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS characteristics make AWS cost effective for a workload with dynamic user demand? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. High availability", "B. Shared security model", "CORRECT:C. Elasticity", "CORRECT:D. Pay-as-you-go pricing", "E. Reliability"],"explanation": "","discussions": "7"}, "Question #3 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are characteristics of Amazon S3? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. A global file system", "CORRECT:B. An object store", "C. A local file store", "D. A network file system", "E. A durable storage system"],"explanation": "","discussions": "29"}, "Question #4 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which services can be used across hybrid AWS Cloud architectures? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon Route 53", "CORRECT:B. Virtual Private Gateway", "C. Classic Load Balancer", "D. Auto Scaling", "E. Amazon CloudWatch default metrics"],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.stratoscale.com/blog/cloud/building-hybrid-cloud-environment-using-amazon-cloud/","discussions": "34"}, "Question #5 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS tools assist with estimating costs? (Select three.)", "answers":[ "A. Detailed billing report", "CORRECT:B. Cost allocation tags", "CORRECT:C. AWS Simple Monthly Calculator", "CORRECT:D. AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator", "E. Cost Estimator"],"explanation": "","discussions": "21"}, "Question #6 Topic 2":{ "question":"AWS supports which of the following methods to add security to Identity and Access Management (IAM) users? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Implementing Amazon Rekognition", "B. Using AWS Shield-protected resources", "C. Blocking access with Security Groups", "CORRECT:D. Using Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)", "CORRECT:E. Enforcing password strength and expiration"],"explanation": "","discussions": "2"}, "Question #7 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS services should be used for read/write of constantly changing data? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Glacier", "CORRECT:B. Amazon RDS", "C. AWS Snowball", "CORRECT:D. Amazon Redshift", "E. Amazon EFS"],"explanation": "","discussions": "19"}, "Question #8 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are features of Amazon CloudWatch Logs? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Summaries by Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)", "B. Free Amazon Elasticsearch Service analytics", "C. Provided at no charge", "CORRECT:D. Real-time monitoring", "CORRECT:E. Adjustable retention"],"explanation": "","discussions": "20"}, "Question #9 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are valid ways for a customer to interact with AWS services? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Command line interface", "B. On-premises", "C. Software Development Kits", "CORRECT:D. Software-as-a-service", "E. Hybrid"],"explanation": "","discussions": "30"}, "Question #10 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following AWS services can be used to serve large amounts of online video content with the lowest possible latency? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. AWS Storage Gateway", "CORRECT:B. Amazon S3", "C. Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)", "D. Amazon Glacier", "CORRECT:E. Amazom CloudFront"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/tutorials/deliver-content-faster/ https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","discussions": "15"}, "Question #11 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following security-related services does AWS offer? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Multi-factor authentication physical tokens", "B. AWS Trusted Advisor security checks", "CORRECT:C. Data encryption", "CORRECT:D. Automated penetration testing", "E. Amazon S3 copyrighted content detection"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/security/","discussions": "22"}, "Question #12 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are categories of AWS Trusted Advisor? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Fault Tolerance", "B. Instance Usage", "C. Infrastructure", "CORRECT:D. Performance", "E. Storage Capacity"],"explanation": "Like your customized cloud expert, AWS Trusted Advisor analyzes your AWS environment and provides best practice recommendations in five categories: cost optimization, performance, security, fault tolerance and service limits. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #13 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following services could be used to deploy an application to servers running on-premises? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. AWS Elastic Beanstalk", "CORRECT:B. AWS OpsWorks", "CORRECT:C. AWS CodeDeploy", "D. AWS Batch", "E. AWS X-Ray"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/codedeploy/latest/userguide/instances-on-premises.html https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/opsworks-on-prem-and-existing-instances/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #14 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which design principles for cloud architecture are recommended when re-architecting a large monolithic application? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Use manual monitoring.", "B. Use fixed servers.", "C. Implement loose coupling.", "CORRECT:D. Rely on individual components.", "CORRECT:E. Design for scalability."],"explanation": "Rearchitecting applications involves sweeping change where an old monolithic application is completely revamped according to modern microservices architecture. Using individual components to re-architect a big application is one part of the process. The most important part is to design the application for scalability because the level of investment for a monolithic application can only be justified when resilience and scalability is needed. Reference: https://www.architech.ca/re-architect-applications/","discussions": "20"}, "Question #15 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS services are defined as global instead of regional? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon Route 53", "B. Amazon EC2", "C. Amazon S3", "CORRECT:D. Amazon CloudFront", "E. Amazon DynamoDB"],"explanation": "Reference: http://jayendrapatil.com/aws-global-vs-regional-vs-az-resources/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #16 Topic 2":{ "question":"The financial benefits of using AWS are: (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. reduced Total Cost of Ownership (TCO).", "CORRECT:B. increased capital expenditure (capex).", "C. reduced operational expenditure (opex).", "D. deferred payment plans for startups.", "E. business credit lines for stratups."],"explanation": "A core reason organizations adopt a cloud IT infrastructure is to save money. The traditional approach of analyzing Total Cost of Ownership no longer applies when you move to the cloud. Cloud services provide the opportunity for you to use only what you need and pay only for what you use. We refer to this new paradigm as the Total Cost of Operation. You can use Total Cost of Operation (TCO) analysis methodologies to compare the costs of owning a traditional data center with the costs of operating your environment using AWS Cloud services. A pay-as-you-go model reduces investments in large capital expenditures. In addition, you can reduce the operating expense (OpEx) costs involved with the management and maintenance of data. This frees up budget, allowing you to quickly act on innovative initiatives that can't be easily pursued when managing CapEx. Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/total-cost-of-operation-benefits-using-aws.pdf","discussions": "38"}, "Question #17 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following can an AWS customer use to launch a new Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) cluster? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Concierge", "B. AWS CloudFormation", "C. Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3)", "D. Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling", "CORRECT:E. AWS Management Console"],"explanation": "","discussions": "17"}, "Question #18 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following security measures protect access to an AWS account? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Enable AWS CloudTrail.", "CORRECT:B. Grant least privilege access to IAM users.", "C. Create one IAM user and share with many developers and users.", "D. Enable Amazon CloudFront.", "CORRECT:E. Activate multi-factor authentication (MFA) for privileged users."],"explanation": "If you decided to create service accounts (that is, accounts used for programmatic access by applications running outside of the AWS environment) and generate access keys for them, you should create a dedicated service account for each use case. This will allow you to restrict the associated policy to only the permissions needed for the particular use case, limiting the blast radius if the credentials are compromised. For example, if a monitoring tool and a release management tool both require access to your AWS environment, create two separate service accounts with two separate policies that define the minimum set of permissions for each tool. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/security/guidelines-for-protecting-your-aws-account-while-using-programmatic-access/","discussions": "7"}, "Question #19 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which options does AWS make available for customers who want to learn about security in the cloud in an instructor-led setting? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. AWS Trusted Advisor", "B. AWS Online Tech Talks", "CORRECT:C. AWS Blog", "D. AWS Forums", "CORRECT:E. AWS Classroom Training"],"explanation": "AWS Training and Certification builds your competence, confidence, and credibility through practical cloud skills that help you innovate and build your future. Our content is built by experts at AWS and updated regularly so you're always learning the latest and keeping your cloud skills fresh. Amazon offer both digital and classroom training including private on-site training. You can choose to learn online at your own pace or learn from an accredited AWS instructor. Whether you're just starting out, building on existing IT skills, or sharpening your cloud knowledge, AWS Training and Certification can help you be more effective and do more in the cloud. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/training/course-descriptions/","discussions": "18"}, "Question #20 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following features can be configured through the Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) Dashboard? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Amazon CloudFront distributions", "B. Amazon Route 53", "CORRECT:C. Security Groups", "CORRECT:D. Subnets", "E. Elastic Load Balancing"],"explanation": "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) lets you provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud where you can launch AWS resources in a virtual network that you define. You have complete control over your virtual networking environment, including selection of your own IP address range, creation of subnets, and configuration of route tables and network gateways. You can use both IPv4 and IPv6 in your VPC for secure and easy access to resources and applications. You can easily customize the network configuration for your Amazon VPC. For example, you can create a public-facing subnet for your web servers that has access to the Internet, and place your backend systems such as databases or application servers in a private-facing subnet with no Internet access. You can leverage multiple layers of security, including security groups and network access control lists, to help control access to Amazon EC2 instances in each subnet. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #21 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS services can be used to gather information about AWS account activity? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Amazon CloudFront", "B. AWS Cloud9", "CORRECT:C. AWS CloudTrail", "D. AWS CloudHSM", "CORRECT:E. Amazon CloudWatch"],"explanation": "AWS offers a solution that uses AWS CloudTrail to log account activity, Amazon Kinesis to compute and stream metrics in real-time, and Amazon DynamoDB to durably store the computed data. Metrics are calculated for create, modify, and delete API calls for more than 60 supported AWS services. The solution also features a dashboard that visualizes your account activity in real-time. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/solutions/real-time-insights-account-activity/","discussions": "7"}, "Question #22 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following common IT tasks can AWS cover to free up company IT resources? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Patching databases software", "CORRECT:B. Testing application releases", "C. Backing up databases", "D. Creating database schema", "CORRECT:E. Running penetration tests"],"explanation": "","discussions": "27"}, "Question #23 Topic 2":{ "question":"What can AWS edge locations be used for? (Select TWO.)", "answers":[ "A. Hosting applications", "CORRECT:B. Delivering content closer to users", "C. Running NoSQL database caching services", "CORRECT:D. Reducing traffic on the server by caching responses", "E. Sending notification messages to end users"],"explanation": "CloudFront delivers your content through a worldwide network of data centers called edge locations. When a user requests content that you're serving with CloudFront, the user is routed to the edge location that provides the lowest latency (time delay), so that content is delivered with the best possible performance. Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/Introduction.html","discussions": "3"}, "Question #24 Topic 2":{ "question":"Access keys in AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) are used to:", "answers":[ "A. log in to the AWS Management Console.", "CORRECT:B. make programmatic calls to AWS from AWS APIs.", "C. log in to Amazon EC2 instances.", "D. authenticate to AWS CodeCommit repositories."],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_access-keys.html","discussions": "2"}, "Question #25 Topic 2":{ "question":"What are the benefits of using the AWS Cloud for companies with customers in many countries around the world? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Companies can deploy applications in multiple AWS Regions to reduce latency.", "B. Amazon Translate automatically translates third-party website interfaces into multiple languages.", "CORRECT:C. Amazon CloudFront has multiple edge locations around the world to reduce latency.", "CORRECT:D. Amazon Comprehend allows users to build applications that can respond to user requests in many languages.", "E. Elastic Load Balancing can distribute application web traffic to multiple AWS Regions around the world, which reduces latency."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/comprehend/features/ https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","discussions": "16"}, "Question #26 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service handles the deployment details of capacity provisioning, load balancing, Auto Scaling, and application health monitoring?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Config", "CORRECT:B. AWS Elastic Beanstalk", "C. Amazon Route 53", "D. Amazon CloudFront"],"explanation": "Explanation - Upload your code and Elastic Beanstalk automatically handles the deployment, from capacity provisioning, load balancing, auto-scaling to application health monitoring. At the same time, you retain full control over the AWS resources powering your application and can access the underlying resources at any time. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #27 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service provides inbound and outbound network ACLs to harden external connectivity to Amazon EC2?", "answers":[ "A. AWS IAM", "B. Amazon Connect", "CORRECT:C. Amazon VPC", "D. Amazon API Gateway"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/VPC_Security.html","discussions": "2"}, "Question #28 Topic 2":{ "question":"When a company provisions web servers in multiple AWS Regions, what is being increased?", "answers":[ "A. Coupling", "CORRECT:B. Availability", "C. Security", "D. Durability"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #29 Topic 2":{ "question":"The pay-as-you-go pricing model for AWS services:", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. reduces capital expenditures.", "B. requires payment up front for AWS services.", "C. is relevant only for Amazon EC2, Amazon S3, and Amazon RDS.", "D. reduces operational expenditures."],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.10thmagnitude.com/opex-vs-capex-the-real-cloud-computing-cost-advantage/","discussions": "7"}, "Question #30 Topic 2":{ "question":"Under the AWS shared responsibility model, AWS is responsible for which security-related task?", "answers":[ "A. Lifecycle management of IAM credentials", "CORRECT:B. Physical security of global infrastructure", "C. Encryption of Amazon EBS volumes", "D. Firewall configuration"],"explanation": "Reference: https://cloudacademy.com/blog/aws-shared-responsibility-model-security/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #31 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service enables users to consolidate billing across multiple accounts?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon QuickSight", "CORRECT:B. AWS Organizations", "C. AWS Budgets", "D. Amazon Forecast"],"explanation": "You can use the consolidated billing feature in AWS Organizations to consolidate billing and payment for multiple AWS accounts or multiple Amazon Internet Services Pvt. Ltd (AISPL) accounts. Every organization in AWS Organizations has a master (payer) account that pays the charges of all the member (linked) accounts. Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/consolidated-billing.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #32 Topic 2":{ "question":"Under the AWS shared responsibility model, which of the following is an example of security in the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. Managing edge locations", "CORRECT:B. Physical security", "C. Firewall configuration", "D. Global infrastructure"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "20"}, "Question #33 Topic 2":{ "question":"How can an AWS user with an AWS Basic Support plan obtain technical assistance from AWS?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Senior Support Engineers", "B. AWS Technical Account Managers", "CORRECT:C. AWS Trusted Advisor", "D. AWS Discussion Forums"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/faqs/","discussions": "12"}, "Question #34 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Multiple Availability Zones", "CORRECT:B. Performance efficiency", "CORRECT:C. Security", "D. Encryption usage", "E. High availability"],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/architecture/AWS_Well-Architected_Framework.pdf (5)","discussions": "4"}, "Question #35 Topic 2":{ "question":"After selecting an Amazon EC2 Dedicated Host reservation, which pricing option would provide the largest discount?", "answers":[ "A. No upfront payment", "B. Hourly on-demand payment", "C. Partial upfront payment", "CORRECT:D. All upfront payment"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/pricing/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #36 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is an advantage of deploying an application across multiple Availability Zones?", "answers":[ "A. There is a lower risk of service failure if a natural disaster causes a service disruption in a given AWS Region.", "CORRECT:B. The application will have higher availability because it can withstand a service disruption in one Availability Zone.", "C. There will be better coverage as Availability Zones are geographically distant and can serve a wider area.", "D. There will be decreased application latency that will improve the user experience."],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","discussions": "4"}, "Question #37 Topic 2":{ "question":"A Cloud Practitioner is asked how to estimate the cost of using a new application on AWS. What is the MOST appropriate response?", "answers":[ "A. Inform the user that AWS pricing allows for on-demand pricing.", "CORRECT:B. Direct the user to the AWS Simple Monthly Calculator for an estimate.", "C. Use Amazon QuickSight to analyze current spending on-premises.", "D. Use Amazon AppStream 2.0 for real-time pricing analytics."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/estimating-aws-resource-costs/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #38 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company wants to migrate its applications to a VPC on AWS. These applications will need to access on-premises resources. What combination of actions will enable the company to accomplish this goal? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Use the AWS Service Catalog to identify a list of on-premises resources that can be migrated.", "CORRECT:B. Build a VPN connection between an on-premises device and a virtual private gateway in the new VPC.", "C. Use Amazon Athena to query data from the on-premises database servers.", "CORRECT:D. Connect the company's on-premises data center to AWS using AWS Direct Connect.", "E. Leverage Amazon CloudFront to restrict access to static web content provided through the company's on-premises web servers."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/apn/amazon-vpc-for-on-premises-network-engineers-part-one/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #39 Topic 2":{ "question":"A web application running on AWS has been spammed with malicious requests from a recurring set of IP addresses. Which AWS service can help secure the application and block the malicious traffic?", "answers":[ "A. AWS IAM", "B. Amazon GuardDuty", "C. Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)", "CORRECT:D. AWS WAF"],"explanation": "Explanation - AWS WAF is a web application firewall that helps protect web applications from common web exploits that could affect application availability, compromise security, or consume excessive resources. You can use AWS WAF to define customizable web security rules that control which traffic accesses your web applications. If you use AWS Shield Advanced, you can use AWS WAF at no extra cost for those protected resources and can engage the DRT to create WAF rules. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/answers/networking/aws-ddos-attack-mitigation/","discussions": "7"}, "Question #40 Topic 2":{ "question":"Treating infrastructure as code in the AWS Cloud allows users to:", "answers":[ "A. automate migration of on-premises hardware to AWS data centers.", "B. let a third party automate an audit of the AWS infrastructure.", "C. turn over application code to AWS so it can run on the AWS infrastructure.", "CORRECT:D. automate the infrastructure provisioning process."],"explanation": "Reference: https://asperbrothers.com/blog/infrastructure-as-code-aws/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #41 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company requires a dedicated network connection between its on-premises servers and the AWS Cloud. Which AWS service should be used?", "answers":[ "A. AWS VPN", "CORRECT:B. AWS Direct Connect", "C. Amazon API Gateway", "D. Amazon Connect"],"explanation": "Explanation - You can use AWS Direct Connect to establish a private virtual interface from your on-premise network directly to your Amazon VPC, providing you with a private, high bandwidth network connection between your network and your VPC. With multiple virtual interfaces, you can even establish private connectivity to multiple VPCs while maintaining network isolation. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/directconnect/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #42 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service can be used to query stored datasets directly from Amazon S3 using standard SQL?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Glue", "B. AWS Data Pipeline", "C. Amazon CloudSearch", "CORRECT:D. Amazon Athena"],"explanation": "Amazon Athena is defined as 'an interactive query service that makes it easy to analyse data directly in Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) using standard SQL.' So, it's another SQL query engine for large data sets stored in S3. This is very similar to other SQL query engines, such as Apache Drill. But unlike Apache Drill, Athena is limited to data only from Amazon's own S3 storage service. However, Athena is able to query a variety of file formats, including, but not limited to CSV, Parquet, JSON, etc.","discussions": "1"}, "Question #43 Topic 2":{ "question":"AWS CloudFormation is designed to help the user:", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. model and provision resources.", "B. update application code.", "C. set up data lakes.", "D. create reports for billing."],"explanation": "Explanation - AWS CloudFormation provides a common language for you to model and provision AWS and third party application resources in your cloud environment. AWS CloudFormation allows you to use programming languages or a simple text file to model and provision, in an automated and secure manner, all the resources needed for your applications across all regions and accounts. This gives you a single source of truth for your AWS and third party resources. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudformation/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #44 Topic 2":{ "question":"A Cloud Practitioner must determine if any security groups in an AWS account have been provisioned to allow unrestricted access for specific ports. What is the SIMPLEST way to do this?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Review the inbound rules for each security group in the Amazon EC2 management console to check for port 0.0.0.0/0.", "B. Run AWS Trusted Advisor and review the findings.", "C. Open the AWS IAM console and check the inbound rule filters for open access.", "D. In AWS Config, create a custom rule that invokes an AWS Lambda function to review rules for inbound access."],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/WindowsGuide/ec2-security-groups.html","discussions": "16"}, "Question #45 Topic 2":{ "question":"What are the benefits of developing and running a new application in the AWS Cloud compared to on-premises? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. AWS automatically distributes the data globally for higher durability.", "B. AWS will take care of operating the application.", "CORRECT:C. AWS makes it easy to architect for high availability.", "CORRECT:D. AWS can easily accommodate application demand changes.", "E. AWS takes care application security patching."],"explanation": "","discussions": "1"}, "Question #46 Topic 2":{ "question":"A user needs an automated security assessment report that will identify unintended network access to Amazon EC2 instances and vulnerabilities on those instances. Which AWS service will provide this assessment report?", "answers":[ "A. EC2 security groups", "B. AWS Config", "C. Amazon Macie", "CORRECT:D. Amazon Inspector"],"explanation": "Amazon Inspector is an automated security assessment service that helps improve the security and compliance of applications deployed on AWS. Amazon Inspector automatically assesses applications for exposure, vulnerabilities, and deviations from best practices. After performing an assessment, Amazon Inspector produces a detailed list of security findings prioritized by level of severity. These findings can be reviewed directly or as part of detailed assessment reports which are available via the Amazon Inspector console or API. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/inspector/","discussions": "4"}, "Question #47 Topic 2":{ "question":"How can a company isolate the costs of production and non-production workloads on AWS?", "answers":[ "A. Create Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles for production and non-production workloads.", "CORRECT:B. Use different accounts for production and non-production expenses.", "C. Use Amazon EC2 for non-production workloads and other services for production workloads.", "D. Use Amazon CloudWatch to monitor the use of services."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/answers/account-management/aws-multi-account-billing-strategy/","discussions": "4"}, "Question #48 Topic 2":{ "question":"Where can users find a catalog of AWS-recognized providers of third-party security solutions?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Service Catalog", "B. AWS Marketplace", "C. AWS Quick Start", "D. AWS CodeDeploy"],"explanation": "AWS Service Catalog Delivery Partners are APN Consulting Partners who help create catalogs of IT services that are approved by the customer's organization for use on AWS. With AWS Service Catalog, customers and partners can centrally manage commonly deployed IT services to help achieve consistent governance and meet compliance requirements while enabling users to self-provision approved services. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/servicecatalog/partners/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #49 Topic 2":{ "question":"A Cloud Practitioner needs to store data for 7 years to meet regulatory requirements. Which AWS service will meet this requirement at the LOWEST cost?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon S3", "B. AWS Snowball", "C. Amazon Redshift", "CORRECT:D. Amazon S3 Glacier"],"explanation": "S3 Glacier Deep Archive is Amazon S3's lowest-cost storage class and supports long-term retention and digital preservation for data that may be accessed once or twice in a year. It is designed for customers 'particularly those in highly-regulated industries, such as the Financial Services, Healthcare, and Public Sectors ' that retain data sets for 7-10 years or longer to meet regulatory compliance requirements. S3 Glacier Deep Archive can also be used for backup and disaster recovery use cases, and is a cost-effective and easy-to-manage alternative to magnetic tape systems, whether they are on-premises libraries or off-premises services. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/s3/storage-classes/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #50 Topic 2":{ "question":"What are the immediate benefits of using the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Increased IT staff.", "B. Capital expenses are replaced with variable expenses.", "CORRECT:C. User control of infrastructure.", "CORRECT:D. Increased agility.", "E. AWS holds responsibility for security in the cloud."],"explanation": "","discussions": "12"}, "Question #51 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which security service automatically recognizes and classifies sensitive data or intellectual property on AWS?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon GuardDuty", "CORRECT:B. Amazon Macie", "C. Amazon Inspector", "D. AWS Shield"],"explanation": "Explanation - Amazon Macie is a security service that uses machine learning to automatically discover, classify, and protect sensitive data in AWS. Macie recognizes sensitive data such as personally identifiable information (PII) or intellectual property. It provides you with dashboards and alerts that give visibility into how this data is being accessed or moved. Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/macie/latest/userguide/what-is-macie.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #52 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is the purpose of AWS Storage Gateway?", "answers":[ "A. It ensures on-premises data storage is 99.999999999% durable.", "B. It transports petabytes of data to and from AWS.", "C. It connects to multiple Amazon EC2 instances.", "CORRECT:D. It connects on-premises data storage to the AWS Cloud."],"explanation": "Explanation - Moving data to the cloud is not quite as simple as flipping a switch. For companies that have managed their own data centers or server rooms for decades, there are a few steps to consider -- and it's not always wise to pull the plug on an internal infrastructure quite so quickly. If a startup uses on-premise business servers and then experiences unexpected growth, abandoning those servers doesn't make sense (even if the long-term plan is to do exactly that). AWS Storage Gateway is a way to bridge this gap for companies of any size. It's a hybrid storage option that connects on-premise storage including age-old tape backup systems to the cloud in a way that also provides one console to access all storage configurations. Reference: https://www.techradar.com/news/what-is-aws-storage-gateway","discussions": "3"}, "Question #53 Topic 2":{ "question":"What should users do if they want to install an application in geographically isolated locations?", "answers":[ "A. Install the application using multiple internet gateways.", "B. Deploy the application to an Amazon VPC.", "CORRECT:C. Deploy the application to multiple AWS Regions.", "D. Configure the application using multiple NAT gateways."],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","discussions": "3"}, "Question #54 Topic 2":{ "question":"A system in the AWS Cloud is designed to withstand the failure of one or more components. What is this an example of?", "answers":[ "A. Elasticity", "CORRECT:B. High Availability", "C. Scalability", "D. Agility"],"explanation": "Reference: https://wa.aws.amazon.com/wat.question.REL_7.en.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #55 Topic 2":{ "question":"A Cloud Practitioner needs a consistent and dedicated connection between AWS resources and an on-premises system. Which AWS service can fulfill this requirement?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Direct Connect", "B. AWS VPN", "C. Amazon Connect", "D. AWS Data Pipeline"],"explanation": "You can use AWS Direct Connect to establish a private virtual interface from your on-premise network directly to your Amazon VPC, providing you with a private, high bandwidth network connection between your network and your VPC. With multiple virtual interfaces, you can even establish private connectivity to multiple VPCs while maintaining network isolation. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/directconnect/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #56 Topic 2":{ "question":"Within the AWS shared responsibility model, who is responsible for security and compliance?", "answers":[ "A. The customer is responsible.", "B. AWS is responsible.", "CORRECT:C. AWS and the customer share responsibility.", "D. AWS shares responsibility with the relevant governing body."],"explanation": "Security and Compliance is a shared responsibility between AWS and the customer. This shared model can help relieve the customer's operational burden as AWS operates, manages and controls the components from the host operating system and virtualization layer down to the physical security of the facilities in which the service operates. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #57 Topic 2":{ "question":"To use the AWS CLI, users are required to generate:", "answers":[ "A. a password policy.", "B. an access/secret key.", "CORRECT:C. a managed policy.", "D. an API key."],"explanation": "","discussions": "11"}, "Question #58 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service is used to provide encryption for Amazon EBS?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Certificate Manager", "B. AWS Systems Manager", "CORRECT:C. AWS KMS", "D. AWS Config"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/kms/latest/developerguide/services-ebs.html","discussions": "2"}, "Question #59 Topic 2":{ "question":"How does AWS charge for AWS Lambda usage once the free tier has been exceeded? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. By the time it takes for the Lambda function to execute.", "B. By the number of versions of a specific Lambda function.", "CORRECT:C. By the number of requests made for a given Lambda function.", "D. By the programming language that is used for the Lambda function.", "CORRECT:E. By the total number of Lambda functions in an AWS account."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/","discussions": "16"}}}